(Sheldon:)Penny, please, I'm on the horns
of a relationship dilemma.
(Sheldon:)And for the record, I had a full pubis of hair
by the time I was 19.
And for the record:
(Penny:)- So, what are you drinking?
- Well, it's been a rough day.
(Sheldon:)I usually go chamomile tea,
but I don't think that's gonna cut it.
(Penny:)You could have a Long Island iced tea.
(Sheldon:)Will that calm my nerves?
It's calmed the pants off me a couple times.
- Sold.
- Oh.
(Penny:)So the heart you got from the wizard
giving you trouble?
(Sheldon:)The trouble isn't with me, Penny,
it's with your gender.
(Sheldon:)Someday scientists will discover...
(Sheldon:)...that second X chromosome contains
nothing but nonsense and twaddle.
(Penny:)Yeah, Amy told me what happened.
(Penny:)Look, just apologize. It'll warm her twaddle.